This is my interactive AI agent ecosystem dungeon in space
that I have all of my AI agents living inside of.
And I organize them in all these different rooms.
For example, we have the two factory rooms
where they're running their own autonomous businesses out of.
And this conveyor belt
is a representation of the Etsy store it started
that it's almost made $2,000 on and everything.
I don't do any work for this.
It runs itself. Inside of these two rooms here we have an a.
We have an AI research agent that's constantly doing research,
for example,
on the autonomous businesses that it started and its competitors,
to see what inspiration we could take from the competitors
and how we can apply it to our own
autonomous businesses that we build.
We have a whole bunch of crazy ass shit going on
in this entire station here.
And in this video in particular,
I actually want to focus on this room here,
which is the armoury room.
And this is where my agent builds and manages its own skills
on Openclap. And we're gonna open up the terminal here
and you're gonna see actually
all of the accounts and API keys I have connected,
like my YouTube channel, the Etsy store is connected.
And I could just in one place,
see everything that's attached to my AI agents
and what they have access to.
And in the skills tab, we have all of the skills that it Has built
and rather replicated would be a better word.
And we could craft. Like,
if I wanted to build my own skill myself,
I could literally just, like,
you know, choose what type of skill it is,
give it a name, description,
and have it build that out for me.
But the main system we have here is.
This is clawhub, right?
This essentially is a website
you can go on
to download skills that are made by other people on Openclaw.
So these are all different skills
that you can download for your AI agent
that was made by somebody else.
And the issue with this site here is
you can't trust any of these skills,
and you can't trust any of the people that uploaded these skills,
because you might get hacked.
There might be some malware in the skill files that you're downloading.
And I found a way to combat this,
in which I figured I would share with you guys,
because I have my agent download these skills,
and you're probably like, oh,
that's unsafe. No,
it's not. I don't install the skill,
I download it. I have the agent look through the internals of the skill,
and we simply replicate that skill
rather than actually installing the skill made by whoever it is.
So all the skills we have that my openclaw runs on
is just replicated from other people on clawhub.
And this isn't, like,
bad or anything. All these skills are free.
And you can't trust them anyway,
so I would highly recommend,
if you are to get any skills on clawhub,
to just have your agent just replicate the skill
rather than actually install it.
Because I do not trust any of these people here,
and I recommend you don't either.
So I figured I'd give you guys some tips on that.